**4**16-873-2787

ashleythadickal@gmail.com

ashleycodes.dev

in Ashley Thadickal

AshThadickal

# ASHLEY THADICKAL

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

I am a front-end web developer with over ten years of experience applying analytical thinking and creative problem-solving skills to manage client expectations in fast-paced environments. I have a love for continuous learning and look forward to collaborating with an experienced team to apply my experience in HTML5, SCSS, JavaScript, and API Integrations. I am excited to bring ideas to life by way of accessible, user-friendly, and responsive code.

## **SKILLS**

## **Tech Stack**



## Interpersonal Skills

Attention to Detail • Problem-Solving • Analytical Thinking • Communication • Paired Programming • Project Scope Management

# **EDUCATION**

## **Immersive Web Development Bootcamp**

Juno College of Technology	2021-2022
Intro to JavaScript	
Juno College of Technology	2021
Intro to Web Development	
Juno College of Technology	2021
Project Management Course	
Conestoga College	2020
Paralegal Diploma with High Honours	
Sheridan College	2008-2010

#### SELECTED PROJECTS

RoboTrivia

React | API | HTML | SASS | Firebase

LIVE | REPO

A trivia quiz app that utilized a trivia API to display questions of ten to the user. Scores can be submitted to firebase and at the end of the quiz, the top three players are displayed. Try your luck and see if you beat the top scores! The site is responsive and accessible to all users.

A Look at Space: Photos from NASA

React | API | HTML | SASS

LIVE | REPO

React project that takes user input to fetch images based on their search query from NASA's image API. Images are displayed on the screen and users are able to like/unlike the images. Site is responsive and accessible for all users.

Park Weather App

JavaScript | API | HTML | SASS

LIVE | REPO

Paired programming project that stored user input and fetched data from a weather API to provide up-to-date weather information to the user. Fully responsive across various screen sizes.

# CAREER SUMMARY

#### Law Clerk

Pavey Law LLP

2017 - 2021

- Utilized analytical skills to interpret, organize and communicate information.
- Collaborated with colleagues to problem-solve and ensure needs were met efficiently.
- Exercised troubleshooting skills to assist with the use of new technologies.
- Used effective communication with various stakeholders; able to tailor the message to meet the needs of the stakeholder.

#### Legal Assistant / Law Clerk Roles

Legal Assistant / Law Clerk Roles	
Dutton Brock LLP	2014-2016
Sal Guzzo, LL.B. Professional Corporation	2013-2014
D'Angela Fox Vanounou LLP	2012-2013
Pro-Bono Law Ontario	2010-2012